

NÈN TẢNG TUYỂN DỤNG NHÂN SỰ HÀNG ĐẦU VIỆT NAM

Ứng viên Bao L. | Nguồn tuyendung.topcv.vn



Bao L.

IOS Developer



□ protected@topcv.vn □ [protected data] □ Ho Chi Minh

ABOUT

Junior iOS developer with more than 1 year experience in developing iOS application. I do my work with attitudes and always seek for better solutions in order to deliver the finest product. I'm looking for a company where I can work in long term and contribute as much as I can.

EDUCATION

Hoa Sen University

August 2016 - Now

Major: Software Engineering

WORK EXPERIENCE

EBIZWORLD

June 2019 - December 2019

Intern & Full-time iOS Developer

Main responsibilities:

- Create UIs from our UI/UX team's designs
- Fix bugs
- Optimize code
- Maintain code
- Apply new features

Recognition and Gains: Recognition and Gains.

- Got an official role in iOS team after finishing 2 months internship, joined 2 projects, learned new technologies, improved company's products and fixed bugs

TMA

Sept 2020 - Now

Full-time iOS Developer

Main responsibilities:

- Develop a new iOS application
- Analyze requirements and design architecture
- Implement features
- Learn Objective C to fix some bugs of an existing project

Recognition and Gains:

- Known how to analyze and design a product from scratch, learned

new technologies and understood deeper about Swift language. Familiar with Objective C and third party library.

PROJECTS

DRAW, MARKUP, RULER

TMA

March 2019 - June 2019

- User can use this app to measure things from a picture. You can add a ruler that can be moved, stretched, add multiple stretchable middle knot. It also allows you to add a pushpin to take note, add text, video, audio as well.
- This app was mostly done by playing with CGPoint and Logic
- Technologies used: Swift, Xcode

HALP USER & DRIVER

EBIZWORLD

Sept 2019 - Dec 2019

- These are booking car applications for both user and driver, they had been published in Singapore when I joined. My role in the team was to fix bugs, maintain and optimize codes and apply new features
- Technologies used: Swift, Firebase, Alamofire, Swifty JSON and RESTful API

BIGCOSM

EBIZWORLD

June 2019 - Sept 2019

- This is an e-wallet application, which was still in the first stage of development. My role was to create UIs and applied some features such as: Transaction history, catching notifications from Firebase, auto logout, QR Scan
- Technologies used: Swift, Firebase, Moya, Swifty JSON and RESTful API

PATITENT MANAGEMENT APP

School Project

March 2019 - June 2019

- This application helps patients from a clinic to manage their informations like appointment schedules, previous appointment, bills, prescription and booking appointment.
- Technologies used: Swift, Xcode, Firebase Database

TECHNICAL SKILLS AND TOOLS

Swift Experienced, know the fundamentals and used in school and company's

projects

Objective C Familiar

C, C# Experienced, know the fundamentals and used in school projects

RESTful API Experienced in using RESTful API and handling JSON

Push Notification Worked with Firebase push notification

Core Data Familiar

Architecture Pattern Experienced with MVP and familiar with MVVM's concept

Third party libraries Experienced with Swifty JSON, Moya, Alamofire

OOP Experienced Firebase Experienced

SOFT SKILLS

Critical thinking Having an the to think clearly and rationally, understanding the logical

connection between ideas

860 points in an internal TOEIC test. Able to write, read, listen and speak English

at intermediate level

Adaptability Having no problem with learning new things and get used to new working

environment

Having an ability to tackle unexpected problems and resolves conflicts **Problem Solving**

Teamwork Worked effectively in a team